Okay, we're coming back over to our dog
page again. Um,
we're pretending that this was
accidentally added where we have two
cards of the same thing. We're going to
call the remove me and we're going to
pass the event. Right now, the way the
remove me function works is I said go to
the event, grab the target element, and
remove it. Now, if you think through
this very carefully, you'll remember
that the target element is what we
clicked. The current target is the one
that has the event handler. So, let's
show you some strange things that happen
with this. So, let's say I want to
delete this card, but I'm hovering over
the H tag. I don't remember which level
H tag it is, but I'm hovering over the H
tag. If I click on it, it deletes it,
but it didn't delete the card. What I
wanted to delete was the card. And if we
come back over, you'll notice that the
card is the one that has the onclick
event. Um, oh, I guess it's just a
Pclass with name or P tag with name on
it. But this is what I clicked and
that's what got removed. And that is
because I did the target. If I want to
remove the thing that has the event
handler on it, then I need to use
current target. So I'll say
event.current
target.
And now if we come over here, if I click
on the H1 tag, it removes the entire
card. And you can see that the other
card then expanded to take up the slice.